<add>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">0</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">SPIRIT OF TRUTH

Brother Joseph Coleman

Local Christian Assembly

41 West 35th Street

New York City, New York

April 25th, 1965</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">1</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Let us bow out heads. Almighty God, we’re so happy this morning Father, that we could come into the House of God. And father, where thou hast prepared our hearts that we may worship thee, the only and true God, in Spirit and in truth.

Lord thy Word is truth, Father, thou hast gathered thy sheep, out of different denominations, and placed us Lord. Predestinated elected seed of God. Thou hast gathered here this morning. Father, we pray Lord knowing in ourselves we can do nothing. We’re insufficient in ourselves to help these people this morning. But Lord, God, thou art the bishop of our souls this morning; The shepherd of our souls Father.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">2</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Thou art able Lord God to feed us this morning. Lord God. Father we’re crying aloud, unto thy Holy Hills. We know that we will hear from Heaven this morning. Lord. For your Word is truth Lord. This the hour Lord, when you’re pouring, issuing forth, words of eternal life, Lord God may these words of eternal life come into our souls, and remain in our hearts Lord.

Father may our hearts be enlarged this morning. Father, to receive all the Words of God this morning. Father we would pray Lord, if there’d be any binding spirits upon the pe ople, any afflicting demons in the Name of Jesus Christ, Lord God, we curse and bind all spirits Lord, that would be against the Holy spirit, the Word of truth this morning.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">3</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Father may your word have free course this morning. Heal the sick and cast out devils Lord, and baptize the sanctified ones, with the Holy Ghost and fire this morning. Father anoint your servant Lord, thou knowest what I’m to speak Lord, this morning Father, may you speak Words of eternal life to the people. Father we commit our souls and our bodies into thy hands this morning. Lord may you bless us with thy Word. For we ask it in Jesus Name Amen. You may be seated.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">4</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Well it’s good to be in the house of God this morning been having quite a battle all week, as to what to speak this morning. Went down to Indiana last weekend, and didn’t get any sleep down there for two nights. Brother Bob Lambert, and myself.

And then I found out this week that God’s Prophet said, that the place is cursed down there. It’s worse down there now. It’s very hard to even fellowship, and worship the Lord down there. I understand, that it’s better to live eighty miles away, from the place and come there and then worship. But however be it as it may, it’s God has ordained the place, where the Words of God might go forth. So we thank the Lord for all things.

So this morning, I pray that you pray with me, and whatever the Lord has laid upon my heart, that He’ll bring it out to you this morning. We know that…</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">5</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">I like to read from St. John the 14th chapter, the 13th through the 26th verse inclusive. And II Timothy the 1st Chapter, 7th through the 10th verse.

And revelation the 3rd chapter, 22nd verse. I’ll read from St. John first, 14th chapter,

   And whatsoever ye shall ask in my name, that will I do,        that the father may be glorified in the Son. If ye shall ask any thing in my name, I will do it.

If ye love me keep my commandments. And I will pray the Father, and he shall give you another comforter, that he may abide with you for ever;

Even the spirit of truth; whom the world cannot receive, because it seeth him not, neither knoweth

him; but ye know him; for he dwelleth with you, and shall be in you.

I will not leave you comfortless: I will come to you. Yet a little while, and the world seeth me no more; but ye shall ye see me: because I live, ye shall live also.

At that day ye shall know that I am in my Father, and ye in me, and I in you. He that hath my commandments, and keepeth them, he it is that loveth me: and he that loveth me shall be loved of my father, and I will love him, and will manifest myself to him.

Those that keep His commandments. Judas saith unto him, not Iscariot, Lord, how is it that thou wilt manifest thyself unto us, and not unto the world?

Jesus answered and said unto him. If a man love me, he will keep my words: and my father will love him, and we will come unto him, and make our abode with him.

He that loveth me and keepeth not my sayings: and the word which ye hear is not mine, but the father’s which sent me. These things have I spoken unto you, being yet present with you.

But the comforter, which is the Holy Ghost, whom the Father will send in my name, he shall teach you all things, and bring all things to your remembrance, whatsoever I have said unto thee.

Peace I leave with you, my peace I give unto you: not as the world giveth, give I unto you. Let not your heart be troubled, neither let it be afraid.

11 Timothy 7th verse

For God hath not given us the spirit of fear; but of power, and of love, and of a sound mind.

Be not thou therefore ashamed of the testimony of our Lord, nor of me his prisoner: but be thou partaker of the afflictions of the gospel according to the power of God.

Who hath saved us, and called us with an holy calling, not according to our works, but according to his own purpose and grace, which was given us in Christ Jesus before the world began,

We receive all these things before the world began.

But is now made manifest by the appearing of our Saviour Jesus Christ, who hath abolished death, and hath brought life and immortality to light through the gospel:

Revelation 3:22.

He that hath an ear, let him hear what the Spirit saith unto the churches.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">6</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">May God add a blessing to the reading of His Word. Like to give it a little title. “Spirit of Truth.” I say Spirit of Truth, because there are many spirits. John said, “Beloved believe not every spirit, that entereth into the world, but try all the spirits by the Word of God.”

He also exhorted us, Paul exhorted Timothy, when he was going over to Macedonia, he had to cross over a body of water. And the Holy Spirit had forbid him to preach any longer over in Asia He had to go over to Europe and He told Timothy to abide, remain in Ephesus. And in Ephesus, charge those that teach some other doctrine, charge them to teach sound doctrine, charge

them to teach sound doctrine and do not give heed to fables and endless genealogies, which gender strife.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">7</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">And therefore, if we are now in Ephesians, we can see that God’s prophet is crossing a great body of water to go to Africa. At the same time. His ministers, they are charged to preach the Word. No other gospel but the Word of God. And we find that, in this end time endless number of seducing spirits have moved men on the Word, and all of those who don’t have the Holy Ghost, these spirits begin to come with endless fables and also genealogies, all kind of doctrines of devils.

Anything to turn you away from the Word of God. But however, the Bible tells us. “He that hath an ear, let him h ear, what the spirit (the Holy Spirit) saith unto the churches.” Now the Holy Spirit is the scriptures, the Word of God. Therefore in this hour, satan is speaking by many different means and also mediums. And so therefore, Paul said, “If an Angel come from heaven and preach any other Gospel let him be accursed”.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">8</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Therefore in this hour we have people (men and woman) having all kind of private revelations, from tapes, and from dreams, and visions and so forth. Men are getting together and trying to figure it out. Doctors and so forth of Divinity are trying to figure out, what is the Holy Ghost. They’re all, trying to do these things. But however, the Word says, “he that hath an ear, let him hear what the Spirit says unto the church.”

Therefore the Holy Spirit of God can only speak through the Word of God. That’s all. All other ground is sinking sand. Only can He speak through the Word. For heaven and earth shall pass away, but my Word shall never pass away. Therefore, we find Jesus Christ as our example. For Jesus Christ whenever they come to him, he said, “Search the Scriptures, for i n there you

think that you have eternal life; and they are they which testify of me.”</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">9</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Therefore if you want to know anything what’s going on today, don’t listen to some kind of private revelation from some woman or man, but search the scriptures, for in there you think you have eternal life, they are they which testify of the Lord Jesus Christ in this hour.

And therefore, because of all this confusion in this hour, God had to send Malachi 4. Knowing that Malachi 4 would return, restore our hearts from all this confusion around here, to the Word of God. And just before God’s Prophet would come out and really nail down the Baptism of the Holy Ghost last Sunday morning. His prophet would come forward and say that

… there’s … be many questions, they will be asked o n the Holy Ghost and different things. But mostly on the Holy Ghost.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">10</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">For in this ministry, very few of the elected seed, have the Holy Ghost. And therefore God knows, this here it’s all for a purpose, for He wants a Word born Bride. And therefore, if you want to understand it, all you have to do is to search the scriptures and begin to read. Jesus Christ three and a half year ministry, when they did not have the Holy Ghost, but they were fed on the Word.

So therefore, that same thing has happened in this hour, and we find that Timothy… Paul said that we were given these great promises, in Christ Jesus, before the world began. But, Jesus Christ, had to appear, to make it manifest. He had to appear as light, the Word, as light to bring to life what was hidden. When He appeared, He brought to light, all of our… He br ought our salvation to light.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">11</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">So therefore, then, when the Apostles and the rest of the people, they saw, that life then they knew that their salvation has been brought to life, which is the Word of God. So therefore we find that whenever the Spirit of God is speaking, He speaks through the scriptures and the scriptures only.

That’s why Jesus Christ, when He went to have His test, He said, “It is written, it is written.” All the time, “it is written”. And therefore, we have the same test today, and we try to slide around the Word of God, by maybe get a revelation. Maybe get a dream. May be feel a quickening power. But – “it i s written”. You can only defeat the enemy by the Word of God, that is the only way that we can defeat the enemy. So we find that in the Word of God, whenever the church is backslidden as it was now, that God would always… the Spirit would speak to th e people through the Word, the scriptures all the time.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">12</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">And you’ll find out that the first thing that must be said, is to repent. When ever God’s people are in sin and idolatry. He sent a prophet and He said, ‘repent’. Then be instructed i n how to clean up. And then have faith towards God. And move on with God and receive all of God’s promises for that hour. That’s the way it always has been. God would always send a prophet to preach, “Repent”.

Then after the prophets we had a four hundred year lapse, during Malachi and then came John the Baptist. He walked on the scene. He said, “repent for the Kingdom of Heav en is at hand.” After his ministry, he turned it over to Jes us Christ. Jesus Christ he said, “The Time is fulfilled, the kingdom of God is at hand. Therefore repent and believe the Gospel.”</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">13</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">And that same thing turned out to Peter on the day of Pentecost. When the Comforter, the Holy Ghost Himself came

into Peter, and quickened Peter’s heart, quickened His body, quickened His members, his mortal mechanics. And then he said it wasn’t Peter, it was the Holy Ghost. Jesus Chris t Himself, Deity in Peter. He took a hold of his vocal chords and he said, “Repent everyone of you, and be baptized, in the na me of the Lord, Jesus Christ. For the remission of your sins, and you shall receive the gift of the Holy Ghost.”

And after that, the same thing came to Paul, the same Holy Ghost and Paul said, “Repent.” And repent came down through all of the seven church ages. Jesus Christ at Ephesus said, ‘repent’. And Smyrna. Thyatira, Sardis, Philadelphi a, Laodicea. The Holy Ghost said. “repent”, that’s all, “Repent” . And we find that many people do not understand what it means to repent.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">14</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">That’s why they’re sick and weakly and there’s no p ower, there’s no nothing because, they have not repented. They cannot understand, what it means to repent, Jesus Christ He knew that, therefore, that’s why He said. “He that hath an ear , let Him hear what the Spirit, (by the word), saith unto the churches.” Only He that hath an ear, let him hear, what those Spirit is saying, unto the churches.

Therefore now we find that there’s a division here now. Not everybody is going to receive this here, for not everybody can repent. Only the predestinated, elected seed of God, can the repent. And therefore we find that the elected, they will hear it and they will repent, for Jesus Christ said, “Repen t.”</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">15</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">As many as I love, only those, that was in my attributes, in my mind, in my memory before the foundation of the world. Those, ‘I’ll put a Spirit of repentance in their he art’s. Then will I send the Prophet of God, a righteous man with the Word of God, that Spirit of repentance, they’ll hear the Word, for it’ll flash across their heart and they will repent.

Therefore, they have an ear, let him hear, understand, what the Spirit, the Word of God is speaking to the church in this hour. And those, and those only will repent. I mean they will repent. Therefore we find…. Why is this? Because Hi s purpose,

is that we should have a Holy Call. For we’re royal priesthood, a Holy Nation and we should show forth the good praises of God in all of this darkness and apostasy in this hour. But how can we do it? Only by a Spirit, genuine spirit of repentance.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">16</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Now we know that we have seen all kinds of repentance. Worldly sorrow but not Godly sorrow. We know that, we know that when a man starts to drink, he wrecks his life, he is worldly sorry, sorry for what he has done to his life. He is worldly sorry. When husband and wife live unfaithful to one another, they wreck they home life, that’s worldly sorrow, for what they have done to their family and also one another.

And same thing and so on. If a man commits a crime, he goes to jail, he’s sorry, for what he has done to his life. That hasn’t got one thing to do with Godly sorrow. Not one thing. For Godly sorrow, when you have done something, you repent, you turn around, turn away from that cursed thing which you have done. And then you do it no more. That’s Godly sorrow, for you recognize that you’re rebels. You’ve sinned against God.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">17</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Then when you can recognize that you have sinned against God, that is Godly sorrow, working towards repentance. Then all of those who recognize that they have sinned against God. Then when John the Baptist came to their seed, Jesus Christ took those that did repent, for Peter left his fishing business, he left it right there, and followed Jesus Christ. Left mother… Mother, Father, Sister, and brother. And left everything and followed the Word.

Now we find that, the Word of God, in this hour now, all of us here, God has taken us out of different churches, now what has happened now? He’s brought us into a private Ministry of the Word of God. That’s what He’s done. Prior to th e time, God’s prophet said, “This day is this scripture ful filled”.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">18</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Prior to that time, we here, we were in the wilderness hacking and blasting our way through all kind of unbelief.

But now, that it’s finished now. He told you about two months ago, that the Ministry has changed. Now it’s the predestinated elected seed of God that is supposed to have repented and now have come to hear instructions to be chastised, by the Word, because they know that God has given the Spirit of repentance and they want to do this here. Therefore they are zealous of good works, …Good works is to believe on Him and whom He has sent. That’s good works.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">19</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Therefore, you are here, not because you want to be here, because God predestinated you to be here today. That you might hear how you are to live. Live according to the Gospel. Not some dreams, some revelation, but according to the Word of God. Then we find that, when God can get a seed like that there. He takes them into private ministry which is now.

Now in the private ministry, notice now, Jesus Christ when He gave out two fish and five loaves of bread. Turned it and fed the multitude, that was wonderful, in His Ministry. In his three and a half year Word Ministry the multitude went away, when He began to preach doctrine, which we all know, “Ex cept you eat my flesh (the Word), and drink my blood you have no life in you.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">20</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">They didn’t like that, then He turned and gave doctrine to the seventy that followed Him. His disciples that He gave power to cast out devils and so forth. He turned to them and said “What if you see the Son of man which is up in heaven, come down from heaven. And go back to heaven?” And they…. “th is is a

hard saying who can receive this? And they walked no more with Him.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">21</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">Then He turned to his disciples, the elected ones, before the foundation of the world. He said, “will you go also ?” And Peter said, “Lord. Thou only hast the Words of eternal li fe. Where would we go at?” And He said, “yes I know, and one of you is a devil.”

Therefore a devil entered into the Word private ministry, a make believer, Judas. And he came on in there, too also. All predestinated of God and there’s a sickening smirking spirit… that be upon, … it’s a devil see? And when the Word of God goes forth, people will sit and smirk. See? For therefore, not sincerely believing they’re covered by spirits. It takes the preaching of the Word of God to blast that smirk off of their faces.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">22</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">For this is God’s house here. God ordained this place here, to be here, that His sheep might hear His Voice. Therefore the elect, as the elect of God, we must know this morning – this morning, what God has in store for us, as the elect of God.

We find out in St. John 14, that, “Whatsoever, … whatsoever, you shall ask in My Name, that will He give unto you.” That is your promises. Not Father, Son and Holy Ghost, but in my Name. The Lord Jesus Christ, in His name, which is Name above every name, that is named – the Name of the Lord Jesus Christ.</field>
  </doc>
  <doc>
    <field name="id">33</field>
    <field name="quote_id">23</field>
    <field name="message_title">The Spirit Of Truth</field>
    <field name="message_preacher">Kevin Blewett</field>
    <field name="message_place" />
    <field name="message_date">2017-08-09</field>
    <field name="message_quote">We find we have these promises, through His Name, if we love him and keep his commandments. Amen, That’s the condition, if we love Him and keep his commandments, then He calls us His friends. For -- and when he took His Disciples into His private Ministry in St. John 12, that speaks about the – the burnt sacrifice, which is on the outside of the Tabernacle there. For there He said, that He had to die, and go into the ground, and rot.

In St John 13, that’s the … that’s where they were cleansed at. They humbled themselves one to another and washed feet. They were cleansed by the water of the Word. That answers to the laver, outside of the Holy place. But in St. John 14,15,16 and 17, Jesus Christ took His Word seed, into the Holy place, where the Shew bread is at. Where there’s light of the Holy Spirit. And there He began to tell them, “Let not your heart b e troubled. In my Father’s house there are many mansions. If it were not so, I would have told you so.”</field>
  </doc>
</add>